Guide to the George D. Vaill, Associate Secretary, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
George D. Vaill, associate secretary, Yale University, records
1919-1988
RU 66
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
13.55
The records consist of correspondence and administrative records documenting George D. Vaill's tenure as associate secretary.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
Vaill, George D.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-B (YRG 4-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant secretaries.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence and administrative records documenting George D. Vaill's tenure as associate secretary.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Inter-university correspondence and greetings, 1920-1973; Accession 1976-A-006
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Correspondence
    - A-Am (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - An-At (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - B-Bal (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bar-Bene (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Benn-Bl (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bo-Bry (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ca-Cam (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Car-Cat (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ced-Cl (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Co-Da (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - De-Dro (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Dru-Ev (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Fa-Fi (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Fl-Ge (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Gr-Ha (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Hi-Hu (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - I-Jac (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Jar-Ju (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - K-Ky (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - L-Li (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Lo-Lu (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - M-Me (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Mi-Mil (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Min-Missi (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Misso-Mor (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Mou (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Mu-Newm (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Newy (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Ni-No (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - O (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - P-Pi (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Po-Que (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Que-Qui (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - R-Rolo (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Roc-Ros (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Ru-Saint B (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Saint J-Saint V (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Sal-Sou (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Sou-St (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - T-Tr (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Tu (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - U-Wa (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - We (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Wh-Wo (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Wr-Wy (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Greetings
    - 1920-1968 (Box 7)
    - 1963-1973 (Box 6)
- Records, circa 1919-1988; Accession 1990-A-009
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023
  - CORRESPONDENCE AND SUBJECT FILES
    - Baldwin, Abraham, Class of 1772: Correspondence regarding his biography, 1961-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bartholomew, Marshall, Memorial Service, 1978 May 11; 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bartholomew, Marshall: Celebration of his ninetieth birthday and general Glee Club and Band information, 1960-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bartholomew, Marshall: Correspondence, 1958-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bartholomew, Marshall: Correspondence, 1958-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bergin, Thomas G.: Poems, correspondence, and photographs, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Blackall, George: Correspondence regarding Woolsey Hall inscription, 1920-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Blair, Edwin: Retirement, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Blount, Archibald: Blount Avenue, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Bronson, Francis W.: Correspondence regarding publication of "From the Editor's Window", 1966-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bunker, Arthur H.: Correspondence regarding search for a photograph for his widow, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Chauncey, Henry Jr., 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Consul General of the Federal Republic of Germany, Dr. Edgar von Schmidt-Pauli, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Coulter, Francis C.: Obituary, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Curtis, Donald McBurney and Arthur Charles McGowan: Requesting correction in Memorial Service for Class of 1935, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Day, Clarence: Drawings, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Downey, Fairfax: Correspondence regarding "The Yale Batteries" and "The Yale Alumni Banjo Club", 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Edgar, Clyde E., Class of 1962: Correspondence regarding Woolsey Hall inscription, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Fox, Frederick: Princeton Correspondence, 1966-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1956-1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Gundelfinger, George Frederick: The New Fraternity, Circa 1915-1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Gundelfinger, George Frederick: The New Fraternity, Circa 1915-1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Hadley, Arthur T. and Morris: Correspondence from various people regarding possible plagiarism by J. F. Kennedy in his Inaugural Address from Hadley's 1902 Commencement Address, 1966-1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Harkness Family, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Hendrickson, Professor George L.: Ninety-fifth Birthday, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Henning, Basil D., 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Holden, Reuben A., 1964-1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Holden, Reuben A., 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Jones, W. Fontaine: Correspondence with Reuben Holden, 1954-1956 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth Sheldon: Memorial Service and Horace Walpole Papers, 1965-1979 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Light, Richard: Correspondence regarding Vaill's purchase of the Flat-Back, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Mabry, Harry C.: Correspondence regarding Fiftieth Reunion of Class of 1923L, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Mendell, Clarence W.: Memorial Service, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Miller, Ogden D.: Funeral, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Nation, Carrie A.: Copies of Articles and Photographs, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Pierson, George W.: "A Short History of Yale" critiques, 1967-1978 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Rogers, James G. III: "James Gamble Rogers-- Yale Architect", 1968, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Sagendorph, Robb: Yankee Magazine Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Salter, Katherine Hayden: Letter to Albert Whitney Griswold, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - SNAV: Correspondence with Al Crowder of Orville K. Snav and Associates, 1964-1978 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Stoddard, Carlos F., Jr.: Remembrances, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Weiser, Abbie Gail: Correspondence regarding Alpha Sigma Phi Fraternity, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Birthday or retirement parties: Bergin, Pierson, Stoddard, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - YALE HISTORY AND MEMORABILIA
    - Historical Statistics by George W. Pierson, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Historical Statistics by George W. Pierson, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Statistics of Yale Degrees by Alice Bowden: Working notes, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Historical References (Box 5, Folder 61 - 63)
    - Mory's Article, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Mory's Business Matters
      - 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - 1974 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - 1975 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - 1969-1979 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - 1960-1980 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Mory's Cup Songs (Box 6, Folder 73 - 78)
    - Mory's Cup Dinners, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Recording Session with Ashcroft, Bellinger, Barr, Jones, and Vaill: 7" discs, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Whiffenpoof Plaque at Mory's: Correspondence regarding its discovery, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Branford, Connecticut, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Old Saybrook, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Yale and New Haven: Community Relations, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Yale's Move to New Haven, 1917-1962 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Connecticut General Assembly: financial support from, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - University Centers for Rational Alternatives: student unrest in late 1960's, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - May Day Packet, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - May Day, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Yale Architecture, 1958-1971 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Yale Architecture, 1935-1977 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Bricks, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - The Yale Fence (with architectural drawing), 1941-1957 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Communion Table: photograph, undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Relocated Parts of Yale, Circa 1960's (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Cupola and Lions: See also folder #38, "Relocated Parts of Yale", Circa 1960's (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Morgan Statues of Abraham Pierson, 1972-1979 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Smithsonian: Correspondence regarding Yale guns, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Banners and Flags, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Yale Bowl Map, undated (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Bozyan Memorial Organ, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Dwight Chapel: Proposed alterations and renovations, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Dedication of Becton Center, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Dedication of Becton Center: Mailing lists, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Cullman Tennis Courts Dedication, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Kline Biology Laboratory Dedication, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Kline Biology Tower Dedication, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Kline Chemistry Wing Dedication, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Nuclear Structure Laboratory Dedication, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Branford Chapel, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Yale University Press, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - School of Medicine, 1964, 1970, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - The Yale Scene: drafts, undated (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Fraternities and Societies, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Alpha Delta Phi Ledger, 1928-1929 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - The Pundits, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - History of Athletics at Yale, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - The Yale of Antiquity, undated (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Yale Lore, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Commemorative Ode: "Commemorative Poem, A.D. 1919" by Brian Hooker (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Baccalaureate, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Baccalaureate Service, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Latin and the Yale Diploma, undated (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Translation of Latin Yale Diploma: Diploma of Sheppard Bliss Gordy, 1911, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Nathaniel Chauncey Diploma, 1702: Correspondence regarding Yale's purchase of Yale's first diploma, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Admissions History, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - "Left Yale to Enter Service of His Country" Certificates, undated (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Elihu Yale- Wales, 1966-1983 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Elihu Yale- Wales, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Guiding and Visitors, 1966-1974 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Yale Guide Maps, 1964-1969 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Yale Guide Maps: French, undated (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Yale Guide Maps: Spanish, undated (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Yale Guide Maps: Japanese, undated (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - PUBLICATIONS AND PRINTINGS
    - A. Whitney Griswold Memorial Volume: Memorandum by George D. Vaill, June 1, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - A. Whitney Griswold Memorial Volume: George D. Vaill Biography, undated (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - A. Whitney Griswold Memorial Volume: File of quotations deleted from volume and consent to publication forms A-Z, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - A. Whitney Griswold Memorial Volume: Consent to publication forms and related correspondence A-F, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - A. Whitney Griswold Memorial Volume: Consent to publication forms and related correspondence G-Q, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - A. Whitney Griswold Memorial Volume: Consent to publication forms and related correspondence R-Z, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - A. Whitney Griswold Memorial Volume: Letters of condolence to Mrs. A. Whitney Griswold and her replies, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Music at Yale by Marshall Bartholomew
      - "Music at Norfolk": The Norfolk Story, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 143)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Ellen Battell Article and Notes, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 144)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Festivals and Summer School, 1962-1965 (Box 11, Folder 145)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Robbins Battell and Elizabeth LeBaron Robbins, undated (Box 11, Folder 146)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Squire Joseph Battell, undated (Box 11, Folder 147)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Barzelai Treat, undated (Box 11, Folder 148)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Songmaster Darius Phelps, undated (Box 11, Folder 149)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Calendar of Yale Music from 1851 and Inventory of Battell gifts, undated (Box 11, Folder 150)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Introduction and Notes, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 151)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Battell, Stoeckel, miscellaneous, undated (Box 11, Folder 152)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Joseph Battell, undated (Box 11, Folder 153)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Genealogies, Robbins, LeBaron, Battell, undated (Box 11, Folder 154)
      - "Music at Norfolk": Irene Battell Larned, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 155)
      - Marshall Bartholomew correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 156)
      - Section I, undated (Box 11, Folder 157)
      - Yale Glee Club, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 158)
      - Music Groups, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 159)
      - General Topics, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 160)
      - Biographical Sketches, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 161)
      - Background material, undated (Box 12, Folder 162)
      - Photographs of International Choral Festival, 1965-1969 (Box 12, Folder 163)
      - Yale Glee Club--drafts, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 164)
      - Music Groups--drafts, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 165)
      - General Topics: drafts, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 166)
      - General Topics: drafts, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 167)
      - General Topics: drafts, 1967-1980 (Box 12, Folder 168)
      - General Topics: drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 169)
      - Biographical Sketches: drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 170)
      - Biographical Sketches: drafts, 1968-1968 (Box 12, Folder 171)
      - Biographical Sketches: drafts, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 172)
      - Miscellany, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - Historical Register of Yale University, 1701-1937
    - Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 174 - 184)
  - Historical Register of Yale University, 1937-1951
    - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 185 - 187)
    - Yale Obituary Record: Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Historical Register: Correspondence with Norman I. Adams, Jr., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - Historical Register of Yale University, 1951-1968
    - Notes and Correspondence, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Faculty and Their Degrees: A-P, undated (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - Faculty and Their Degrees: R-T, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - Faculty and Their Degrees: U-Z, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 193)
  - "Residential Colleges"
    - Revised "Residential Colleges" Pamphlet, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Proposal for Republication of Pamphlets, 1075-1976 (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Lists of Masters and Deans, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Revised Introduction, undated (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Revised Pamphlet, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Berkeley College: Robert Triffin, undated (Box 16, Folder 199)
    - Calhoun College: Robert Thompson, Acting Master, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 201)
    - Davenport College: Firuz Kazemzadeh, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 202)
    - Timothy Dwight College: Donald Kagan, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 203)
    - Jonathan Edwards College: Edgar Boell, Acting Master, undated (Box 16, Folder 204)
    - Morse College: Richard Granger, undated (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - Pierson College: George Gaddis Smith, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 206)
    - Silliman College: Eli Clark, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - Ezra Stiles: Theodore Lidz, Acting Master, undated (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - Trumbull College: Robert Fogelin, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 210)
  - Buildings and Grounds of Yale
    - Buildings of Yale, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - The Buildings of Yale University: Working Copy with Corrections for Revised Edition, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - The Buildings of Yale University: Working Copy with Corrections for Revised Edition, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 213)
    - Schedule and Preface, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Inserts, undated (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Unnamed Buildings Project, undated (Box 16, Folder 216)
    - New Revisions, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 217)
    - General Information, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 218)
    - Buildings and Memorials, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 219)
    - Richard C. Carroll: Agenda and Miscellaneous Information, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 220)
    - Richard C. Carroll: Inserts for Master Copy, undated (Box 16, Folder 221)
    - Richard C. Carroll: Master Copy, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 222)
    - Early Worksheets, undated (Box 17, Folder 223)
    - Edward W. Y. Dunn: Master Copy, undated (Box 17, Folder 224)
    - Yale University Buildings, undated (Box 17, Folder 225)
    - Yale University Buildings and "Griswold's Building Years at Yale", undated (Box 17, Folder 226)
    - Richard C. Carroll: Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 227)
    - Reuben A. Holden: Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 228)
    - Archives Files, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 229)
  - Faculty Research and Publications from Annual Department Reports, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 230 - 232)
  - Corporation Brochure, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - On Sepulchres by Ugo Fuscolo
    - Thomas Bergin, Deane Keller, and George D. Vaill: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 234)
    - General, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 235)
    - Bergin, Keller and Vaill: Correspondence and Photographs, undated (Box 19, Folder 236)
  - Lecture Given by George D. Vaill, 1974 May 30 (Box 19, Folder 237)
  - Articles for Yale Weekly Bulletin and Calendar, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 238)
  - Weekly Calendar: Correspondence and Complaints, 1966-1976 (Box 19, Folder 239)
  - Articles in the Hartford Courant: Correspondence with Charles Morse, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 240)
  - Corrections for Dexter's Biographies and Annals, undated (Box 19, Folder 241)
  - Speech to North End Club, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 242)
  - The Progenitors of Dudley Landon Vaill and Leila Strobridge Holmes Vaill by George D. Vaill, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 243)
  - Genealogy, 1965-1979 (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - Newspaper Clippings from The World, 1887 June 18 (Box 19, Folder 245)
  - Printing Samples (See also Box 32, Folder 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 246)
  - Printed Materials: Programs and Invitations, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - Printed Materials: Christmas Greetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 248)
  - The Honorable Company of College Printers: Printing Samples, 1973-1976 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Printed Memorabilia
    - 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 250)
    - 1971-1982 (Box 20, Folder 251)
    - 1978 (Box 20, Folder 252)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 253)
    - 1962-1967 (Box 20, Folder 254)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 255)
  - ALUMNI CORREPONDENCE, PRIZES, FELLOWSHIPS AND MEMORIALS
    - Andover Class of 1982: Miscellaneous Items Including Reminiscences by George C. Luke (1977) and W. C. Reed (Reade) (1963), undated (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Hollon A. Farr, Class of 1896: Correspondence with Classmates Regarding Alumni Affairs, 1954-195721 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Hollon A. Farr: Andover Reunions and Alumni Material, Photograph of Andover Class of 1892 in 1928 and Engravings of Andover Buildings. [See also Box 32], 1950-1954 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - Plaques, Tablets, Markers, 1965-1976 (Box 22, Folder 259)
    - Memorials, 1932-1970 (Box 22, Folder 260 - 261)
    - Hippopotami, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 262)
    - Class Day Material: Speeches, 1969, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 263)
  - Class of 1935
    - Thirtieth Reunion, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 264 - 265)
    - Thirtieth Reunion, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 266)
    - Obituaries, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 267)
    - Quarter Century Record, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 268)
    - Correspondence Regarding Printing of Class Letterhead (1965) and Classbook and Quarter Century Record (1960) (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - Letters of Thanks for the Quarter Century Record, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 270)
    - Reunions, Football Game Tents, 1960-1974 (Box 23, Folder 271)
    - Forty-fifth Reunion, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 272)
    - Notes for the Yale Alumni Magazine, 1970-1975 (Box 23, Folder 273)
    - Notes for the Yale Alumni Magazine, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 274)
  - Class of 1938: Reunions, 1961-1975 (Box 23, Folder 275)
  - Class of 1896: Patterson Fund, 1956-1975 (Box 23, Folder 276)
  - Class of 1896: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 23, Folder 277)
  - Yale Alumni Journal, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 278)
  - Alumni Seminar, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 279)
  - Alumni Seminar, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 280)
  - Alumni Day, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 281)
  - Alumni Day, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 282)
  - Alumni Day, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 283)
  - Lux et Veritas, Inc.: Journal, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 284)
  - Elizabethan Club at Yale, 1972-1975 (Box 24, Folder 285)
  - Yale Club, New York, 1965-1974 (Box 24, Folder 286)
  - Football Y Association and Centennial, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 287)
  - Meetings of Former Military at Yale, 1976-1981 (Box 24, Folder 288)
  - Breit Symposium, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 289)
  - Cecil T. Lane Symposium, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Josiah W. Gibbs Centennial, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - James Jackson Jarves Collection Centennial, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 292)
  - Law School: Sesquicentennial, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - Honorary Degree Citations, 1968-1975 (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Yale Medals Struck between 1856 and 1869, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - Yale Medal, 1973-1977 (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Yale Medal, 1970-1977 (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - Howland Prize, 1966-1977 (Box 24, Folder 298)
  - Lohmann Prize, 1965-1977 (Box 25, Folder 299)
  - Adrian van Sinderen '10 Prizes for Book Collecting
    - 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 300)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 301)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 302)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 303)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 304)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 305)
  - Mellon Fellows: Pamphlet, 1932-1967 (Box 25, Folder 308)
  - UNIVERSITY ADMINISTRATIVE AFFAIRS AND PERSONAL MEMORABILIA
    - Miscellaneous University Matters
      - 1965-1969 (Box 26, Folder 309 - 311)
      - 1971 (Box 26, Folder 312)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 313 - 315)
      - 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 316 - 319)
      - 1976 (Box 26, Folder 320)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 321)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 322)
      - 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 323)
      - 1969-1973 (Box 27, Folder 324)
    - Resolutions: Retirements, 1965-1972 (Box 27, Folder 325)
    - Resolutions: Deaths:, 1964-1977 (Box 27, Folder 326)
    - Resolutions: Miscellaneous, 1966-1975 (Box 27, Folder 327)
    - Recording Secretary's Bible, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 329)
    - Council on Priorities and Planning: Report of Committee on the Future of the College and the Graduate School, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 330)
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on the Future of Urban Studies at Yale, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 331)
    - Minority Group Recruitment Proposals, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 332)
    - Equal Job Opportunity Panel, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 333)
    - Art and Architecture, 1973-1977 (Box 28, Folder 334)
    - Art Gallery, 1973-197628 (Box 28, Folder 335)
    - College Affiliations, 1964-1967 (Box 28, Folder 336)
    - New Haven Municipal Affairs, 1960-1963 (Box 28, Folder 337)
    - Delegates to Events at Other Institutions, 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 338)
    - Dartmouth: Notes for Giamiatti's Speech at President's Inauguration, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 339)